var title = "Traduza para grego.";

var questions = [

  {
    prompt: "zero (0)",
    answer: ["μηδέν"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "um (1)",
    answer: ["ένα"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "dois (2)",
    answer: ["δύο"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "três (3)",
    answer: ["τρία"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "quatro (4)",
    answer: ["τέσσερα"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "cinco (5)",
    answer: ["πέντε"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "seis (6)",
    answer: ["έξι"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "sete (7)",
    answer: ["επτά", "εφτά"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "oito (8)",
    answer: ["οκτώ", "οχτώ"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "nove (9)",
    answer: ["εννιά", "εννέα"],
    partial: [],
  },

  {
    prompt: "dez (10)",
    answer: ["δέκα"],
    partial: [],
  },

];
  